(Sheldon:)Worst Renaissance fair ever.
(Leonard:)Please let it go, Sheldon.
SHELDON:
It was rife with historical inaccuracies.
(Sheldon:)For example, the tavern girl
serving flagons of mead.
(Sheldon:)Now, her costume
was obviously Germanic...
(Sheldon:)...but in 1487, the Bavarian purity laws,
or Reinheitsgebot...
(Sheldon:)...severely limited the availability
of mead.
(Sheldon:)At best,
they would've had some spiced wine.
LEONARD: You're nitpicking.
SHELDON: Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)Well, here's another nit for you.
(Sheldon:)The flagons would not have been made
of polypropylene.
(Howard:)Renaissance fairs
aren't about historical accuracy.
(Howard:)They're about taking chubby girls
who work at Kinko's...
(Howard:)...and lacing them up
in corsets so tight...
(Howard:)...their bosom jumps out
and says, "Howdy."
Bosoms would not have said, "Howdy,"
in the 15th century.
(Sheldon:)If anything,
they would've said, "Huzzah."
(Howard:)I don't care what the bosoms say,
Sheldon.
I just wanna be part of the conversation.
(Penny(arriving with a man in tow):)Hi, guys.
(Penny(arriving with a man in tow):)Looks like you've been
to the Renaissance fair.